- 介绍你认识沃尔特  - 好的
- I'm gonna introduce you to Walter.  - Yeah.
老兄 想来杯啤酒什么的吗
Dude, you wanna grab a beer or something?
我的新书会在四月出版 谢谢关心
My new book comes out in April. Thank you for asking.
- 很好  - 是五月
- Great.  - May.
对 是五月 五月
May. May.
这是安德烈 你们俩是《时代》杂志的
This is Andre. You two are times'
最佳名人候选人
most notable nominees.
很高兴终于见到你了
So glad to finally meet you.
Nice to finally meet you.
我喂过他玉米脆饼了 没问题吧
I fed him nachos. Is that bad?
你看起来很舒服
You look comfortable.
你喂他吃什么 三氯甲烷吗[麻醉剂]
What'd you feed him, chloroform?
- 来让你爸爸抱吧  - 我说了 玉米脆饼
- Give him to his dad.  - I told you, nachos.
如果我那样拉一通的话 我也会睡那么香
Know what? I'd be asleep too if l had a dump like that.
- 到妈妈那里去吧  - 来吧
- We'll give him to his mom.  - Come here then.